Guide to the Philip Ross Collection of NLRB Documents 1927-1974
Ross, Philip Collection of NLRB Documents
- 21-CB-2061; Teamsters Union Local 683, 1963 (Box 434, Folder 19)
  (Orange Empire Co-op) National City, CA
- 21-CB-2062; International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local Union 11, District 6, 1963 (Box 434, Folder 20)
  (Steiny Mitchel) Los Angeles, CA
- 21-CB-2063; United Electrical, Radio & Machine Workers of America, 1963 (Box 434, Folder 21)
  (United Superior Record Mfg. Co.) Los Angeles, CA
- 21-CB-2064; Hod Carriers & Construction Laborers Union Local 300, 1963 (Box 434, Folder 22)
  (Anthony Pools, Inc.) South Gate, CA
- 21-CB-2065; Local Freight Drivers, Local 208, International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen & Helpers of America, 1963 (Box 434, Folder 23)
  (Los Angeles-Seattle Motor Express, Inc.) Vernon, CA
- 12-CB-2066; Local Union 1815, United Brotherhood of Carpenters & Joiners of America, 1963 (Box 434, Folder 24)
  (Newberg Construction Company) Orange, CA
- 21-CB-2067; Teamsters Automotive Union, Local 495, 1963 (Box 434, Folder 25)
  (American Wholesale Electric) Los Angeles, CA
- 21-CB-2068; New Furniture & Appliance Drivers, Warehousemen & Helpers, Local 196, Teamsters, 1963 (Box 434, Folder 26)
  (Virtue Brothers Mfg. Co.) Los Angeles, CA
- 21-CB-2069; International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen & Helpers of America, Local 848, 1963 (Box 435, Folder 1)
  (United Vinters Inc.) Los Angeles, CA
- 21-CB-2070; Sheet Metal Workers' International Association, Local Union 509, 1963 (Box 435, Folder 2)
  (Wrights Mfg., Inc.) Colton, CA
- 21-CB-2071; Construction & General Laborers Local Union 591, 1963 (Box 435, Folder 3)
  (Coxco Incorporated) Santa Barbara, CA
- 21-CB-2072; International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen & Helpers of America, Freight Handlers, Clerks & Helpers Local 357, 1963 (Box 435, Folder 4)
- 21-CB-2073; National Marine Engineers Beneficial Association, 1963 (Box 435, Folder 5)
  (Pacific Maritime Association) Wilmington, CA
- 21-CB-2075; Local 11, International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, District 6, 1963 (Box 435, Folder 6)
  (Charles O. Payne Electrical Company, Inc.) Downey, CA
- 21-CB-2078; International Association of Machinists Local Lodge 1893, 1963 (Box 435, Folder 7)
  (Aerojet-General Corporation) Azusa, CA
- 21-CB-2079; Freight Handlers, Clerks & Helpers, Local 357, International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen & Helpers of America, 1963 (Box 435, Folder 8)
- 21-CB-2080-1; Local 743, United Brotherhood of Carpenters & Joiners of America, 1963 (Box 435, Folder 9)
  Bakersfield, CA
- 21-CB-2080-2; Local 1607, United Brotherhood of Carpenters & Joiners of America, 1963 (Box 435, Folder 10)
- 21-CB-2081; C. H. Sutton, Agent of Local 743, United Brotherhood of Carpenters & Joiners of America, 1963 (Box 435, Folder 11)
- 21-CB-2082; General Truck Drivers, Warehousemen & Helpers Union Local 467, 1963 (Box 435, Folder 12)
  (Miles & Sons Trucking Service) Merced, CA
- 21-CB-2084; Local Freight Drivers, Local 208, Line Drivers, Local 224, 1963 (Box 435, Folder 13)
  (Merchant's Express) Montebello, CA
- 21-CB-2085; Printing Trades Union, Inc., 1963 (Box 435, Folder 14)
  (Citizen News) Hollywood, CA
- 21-CB-2086; International Hod Carriers, Building & Common Laborers Union of America, Pomona Local 806, 1963 (Box 435, Folder 15)
  (Artcraft Masonry) La Canada, CA
- 21-CB-2087; International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen & Helpers of America, Local 357, 1963 (Box 435, Folder 16)
  (Western Truck Lines) Los Angeles, CA
- 21-CB-2089; International Union of Operating Engineers, Local Union 12, 1963 (Box 435, Folder 17)
  (E. C. Young - Young Corporation) El Cajon, CA
- 21-CB-2092; Sign, Scene, Pictorial Painters, Display & Decorators, Local Union 831 Brotherhood of Painters, Decorators & Paperhangers of America, 1963 (Box 435, Folder 18)
  (Home Builders Sign Association) Los Angeles, Baldwin Park, Santa Ana, & Garden Grove, CA
- 21-CB-2093; Southern California District Council of Laborers & Local, Hod Carriers & Laborers Local 300, 1963 (Box 435, Folder 19)
  (Norris & Son, Inc.) El Monte, CA
- 21-CB-2094; Southern California Joint Board Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, Local 81, 1963 (Box 435, Folder 20)
  (Robert Hall Clothing Stores) Montclair, CA
- 21-CB-2095; Exhibit File, 1963 (Box 435, Folder 21)
- 21-CB-2097; Miscellaneous Warehousemen, Drivers & Helpers, Local 986, I.B.T.C.W. & H. of A., 1963 (Box 436, Folder 1)
  (Du Bois Chemicals, Inc.) Los Angeles, CA
- 21-CB-2098; Local 652, International Hod Carriers Building & Common Laborers Union of America, 1963 (Box 436, Folder 2)
- 21-CB-1994; Laborers & Hod Carriers' Local 652, 1963 (Box 436, Folder 3)
- 21-CB-2099; Local 2869, United Steelworkers of America, 1963 (Box 436, Folder 4)
  (Kaiser Steel Corporation) Fontana, CA
- 21-CB-2100; Local 652, International Hod Carriers, Building & Common Laborers Union of America, 1963 (Box 436, Folder 5)
- 21-CB-2102; Line Drivers Union Local 224, I.B.T.C.W. & H. of A., 1963 (Box 436, Folder 6)
  (Connolly Transportation, Inc.) Vernon, CA
- 21-CB-2103; Local 9, Industrial Union of Marine & Shipbuilding Workers of America, 1963 (Box 436, Folder 7)
  (Todd Shipyards Corporation, Los Angeles Division) San Pedro, CA
- 21-CB-2105; Carpenters Local Union 1913, Sheet Metal Workers Local Union 108, 1963 (Box 436, Folder 8)
  (Raymond & Diamond Const., The Cooler Man) Van Nuys & Reseda, CA
- 21-CB-2106; Laborers' & Hod Carriers' Union, Local 300, 1964 (Box 436, Folder 9)
- 21-CB-2107; Iron Workers Local 509, W. L. Walter "Blackie" Hill, Business Agent, et al., 1963 (Box 436, Folder 10)
- 21-CB-2108; Waiters Union, Local 17, 1963 (Box 436, Folder 11)
  (Baltimore Hotel, et al.) Los Angeles & Beverly Hills, CA
- 12-CB-2109; International Association of Machinists District Lodge 80, 1963 (Box 436, Folder 12)
  (Huffy Mfg. Co.) Azusa, CA
- 21-CB-2110; Allied Industrial Workers of America Local 976, 1963 (Box 436, Folder 13)
  (Cadet Records, Inc.) Los Angeles, CA
- 21-CB-2111; Iron Workers Shop 627, 1963 (Box 436, Folder 14)
  (Balboa-City Street Works, Inc.) San Diego, CA
- 21-CB-2112; Freight Handlers, Clerk Helpers Local 357, International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen & Helpers of America, 1963 (Box 436, Folder 15)
- 21-CB-2113; International Union of Operating Engineers, Local Union 12, 1963 (Box 436, Folder 16)
- 21-CB-2116; Waiters Union Local 17, 1963 (Box 436, Folder 17)
  (ABC Vending Corporation of California) Los Angeles, CA
- 21-CB-2117; Freight Handlers, Clerks & Helpers Local 357, International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen & Helpers of America, 1963 (Box 436, Folder 18)
- 21-CB-2118; Local 504, International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees & Motion Picture Machine Operators, 1964 (Box 436, Folder 19)
- 21-CB-2119; United Packinghouse, Food & Allied Workers, 1963 (Box 436, Folder 20)
  (Valley Date Gardens, Inc.) Indio, CA
- 21-CB-2120; International Union of United Automobile, Aircraft, & Agricultural Workers of America, 1963 (Box 436, Folder 21)
  (General Motors Corporation, Chevrolet Division) Van Nuys, CA
- 21-CB-2120-2; International Union of United Automobile, Aircraft & Agricultural Workers of America, 1963 (Box 436, Folder 22)
- 21-CB-2120-3; International Union of United Automobile, Aircraft & Agricultural Workers of America, 1963 (Box 436, Folder 23)
- 21-CB-2121; Printing Specialties & Paper Products Union District Council 2 & Printing Specialties & Paper Products Union Local 388, 1963 (Box 436, Folder 24)
  (Colortone Decal Co.) Los Angeles, CA
- 21-CB-2122; United Packing House, Food & Allied Workers & Local 78-B, 1963 (Box 436, Folder 25)
  (Admiral Packing Co.) Somerton, AZ
- 21-CB-2123; Laundry, Dry Cleaning & Dye House Workers' International Union, 1963 (Box 436, Folder 26)
  (Tamkin Towel Service) Los Angeles, CA
- 21-CB-2125; Printing Trades Union, Inc., 1963 (Box 436, Folder 27)
  (Hollywood Citizen News) Los Angeles, CA
- 21-CB-2126; Pile Drivers, Bridge, Wharf, Dock, Carpenters, Welders, Divers, Rig Builders, & Drillers Union 2375, 1963 (Box 436, Folder 28)
  (Caldrill Offshore, Inc., Western Offshore Drilling & Exploration Co.) Ventura & Santa Fe Springs, CA
- 21-CB-2127; United Steel Workers of America, Local 4670, 1964 (Box 436, Folder 29)
  (Aerojet-General Corporation) Downey, CA
- 21-CB-2129; Southern California District Council of Laborers & Affiliated Local 652, 1963 (Box 436, Folder 30)
  (American Pine & Construction Company) Santa Ana, CA
- 21-CB-2130; Lathers Local 460, 1963 (Box 436, Folder 31)
  (Robert Skartvedt Lathing) San Diego, CA
- 21-CB-2131; International Typographical Union, Local 994 & Agents Warren P. Callaghan & William L. Ryan, San Gabriel Valley Daily Tribune, 1963 (Box 436, Folder 32)
  (San Gabriel Valley Newspapers, Inc.) West Covina, CA
- 21-CB-2132; Miscellaneous Warehousemen, Drivers & Helpers, Local 986, I.B.T.C.W. & H. of A., 1963 (Box 436, Folder 33)
  (La Colonial Mexican Foods) Los Angeles, CA
- 21-CB-2133; International Brotherhood of United Slate, Tile & Composition Roofers, Damp & Waterproof Workers Association, Local 36, 1963 (Box 436, Folder 34)
  (Associated Roof & Sheet Metal Co.) Los Angeles, CA
- 21-CB-2134; The Normandie Club, 1963 (Box 437, Folder 1)
  Gardena, CA
- 21-CB-2136; International Union of United Automobile, Aircraft, & Agricultural Workers of America, 1963 (Box 437, Folder 2)
- 21-CB-2137; Iron Workers Local 509, W. L. Walter "Blackie" Hill, Business Agent, et al., 1963 (Box 437, Folder 3)
- 21-CB-2138; Local Lodge755, International Association of Machinists, 1963 (Box 437, Folder 4)
  (Rohr Aircraft Corporation) Chula Vista, CA
- 21-CB-2139; International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite & Paper Mill Workers Union, 1963 (Box 437, Folder 5)
  (Eureka Paper Box Company, Inc.) Los Angeles, CA
- 21-CB-2141; Furniture Workers Union Local 500, 1963 (Box 437, Folder 6)
  (Western Synthetic & Felt Co.) Los Angeles, CA
- 21-CB-2142; Carpet, Linoleum & Soft Tile Local Union 1247, Brotherhood of Painters, 1963 (Box 437, Folder 7)
  (Wakefield Floor Covering & Tile Company) Buena Park, CA
- 21-CB-2144; Teamsters Union Local 871, 1963 (Box 437, Folder 8)
  (Pascal-Ludwig Equipment Co.) Upland, CA
- 21-CB-2148; Marine Cooks & Stewards Union, 1963 (Box 437, Folder 9)
  (M.G.R.S. Company) Wilmington, CA
- 21-CB-2149; International Association of Machinists, 1963 (Box 437, Folder 10)
  (General Dynamics Corporation) Vandenberg Air Force Base, CA
- 21-CB-2150; Los Angeles Newspaper Guild & Agent, 1963 (Box 437, Folder 11)
  (Hillbro Corporation) Los Angeles, CA
- 21-CB-2151; General Truck Drivers Union, Local 235 of International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen & Helpers of America, 1963 (Box 437, Folder 12)
  (Anaconda Wire & Cable Co.) Orange, CA
- 21-CB-2152; Electronic & Space Technicians, Local 1553, 1963 (Box 437, Folder 13)
  (Hughes Aircraft Co., El Segundo Division) Los Angeles, CA
- 21-CB-2153; Local 1052, United Brotherhood of Carpenters & Joiners of America, 1963 (Box 437, Folder 14)
  (Associated General Contractors) Los Angeles, CA
- 21-CB-2154; International Union of Electrical, Radio & Machine Workers, 1963 (Box 437, Folder 15)
  (Altec Lansing Corp.) Anaheim, CA
- 21-CB-2157; Local Union 640, United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum & Plastic Workers of America, 1963 (Box 437, Folder 16)
  (Kentile, Inc.) Torrance, CA
- 21-CB-2158; Communications Workers of America, Southern California Local 9590, 1963 (Box 437, Folder 17)
  (Western Electric Co.) Montebello, CA
- 21-CB-2159; Operative Plasterers & Cement Masons International Association, Local 343, 1963 (Box 437, Folder 18)
  (Francescon Plastering Contractors, Inc.) Arcadia, CA
- 21-CB-2160; Upholsterer's International Union of North America, Local 15A, 1963 (Box 437, Folder 19)
  (Good Furniture Manufacturing Company) Gardena, CA
- 21-CB-2161; Southern California Pipe Trades District Council 16 of United Association, Plumbing-Pipefitting & Refrigeration Industry Local Union 230, 1963 (Box 437, Folder 20)
  (Plumbing Contractors Guild of San Diego County) San Diego, CA
- 21-CB-2163; International Union, Confederated Industrial Workers of America, 1963 (Box 437, Folder 21)
  (Dorwood of California) Pacoima, CA
- 21-CB-2164; Upholsterer's International Union of North America, Local 15A, 1963 (Box 437, Folder 22)
- 21-CB-2165; Brotherhood of Painters, Decorators & Paper Hangers of America, Painters Union Local 1627, Orange Belt District Council of Painters 48, 1963 (Box 437, Folder 23)
  (U. S. Bradley) San Bernardino, CA
- 21-CB-2166; American Newspaper Guild, 1963 (Box 437, Folder 24)
  (News-Press Publishing Co.) Santa Barbara, CA
- 21-CB-2168; United Automobile, Aircraft, Agricultural Implement Workers of America, 1963 (Box 437, Folder 25)
- 21-CB-2169; United Steelworkers of America, Local 2869, 1963 (Box 437, Folder 26)
- 21-CB-2170-1; International Brotherhood of Carpenters & Joiners of America, Local Union 769, 1963 (Box 437, Folder 27)
  (The William Simpson Construction Company) Los Angeles, CA
- 21-CB-2170-2; International Brotherhood of Carpenters & Joiners of America, Local Union 769, 1963 (Box 437, Folder 28)
- 21-CB-2171; Service & Maintenance Employees' Union, Local 399, 1963 (Box 437, Folder 29)
  (Benton Management) Los Angeles, CA
- 21-CB-2172; United Association of Journeymen & Apprentices of Plumbing & Pipe Fitting Industry of US & Canada, Refrigeration Fitters Branch Local Union 250, 1963 (Box 437, Folder 30)
  (Bar-Master, Inc.) Los Angeles, CA
- 21-CB-2173-1; International Association of Heat & Frost Insulators & Asbestos Workers, Local 5 of Los Angeles, CA, 1963 (Box 437, Folder 31)
  (Armstrong Contracting & Supply Corporation) Los Angeles, CA
- 21-CB-2173-2; International Association of Heat & Frost Insulators & Asbestos Workers, Local 5 of Los Angeles, CA, 1963 (Box 437, Folder 32)
  (Fiberglass Engineering & Supply Div., Owens-Corning Fiberglass Corporation) Los Angeles, CA
- 21-CB-2173-3; International Association of Heat & Frost Insulators & Asbestos Workers, Local 5 of Los Angeles, CA, 1963 (Box 437, Folder 33)
  (Thorpe Insulation Company) Los Angeles, CA
- 21-CB-2176; Local 40, International Chemical Workers Union, 1963 (Box 437, Folder 34)
  (U. S. Borax & Chemical Corporation)
- 21-CB-2177; Food, Drug & Beverage Warehousemen & Clerical Employees Local Union 595, International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen & Helpers of America, 1963 (Box 437, Folder 35)
  (Food Giant Markets, Inc.) Santa Fe Springs, CA
- 21-CB-2461; Lathing Joint Conference Board of Southern California, Lathers Union Local 81 & 42A, 1965 (Box 437, Folder 36)
- 21-CB-2554; International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen & Helpers of America, Teamsters Local 848, 1965 (Box 437, Folder 37)
  (Dad's Nesbit's Bottling Co.) Los Angeles, CA
- 1-CC-180; Carpenters, et al., 1959 (Box 438, Folder 1)
  (Leo Spear Const. Co., Inc.) Indianapolis, IN
- 1-CC-180; Springfield Bldg. & Const. Trades Council et al., 1959 (Box 438, Folder 2)
- 1-CC-184; Carpenters' Dist. Council of Springfield, MA, et al., 1959 (Box 438, Folder 3)
  (James F. Rogers, d/b/a Rogers Heating & Engineering Company) West Springfield, MA
- 1-CC-186; Shopmen's Local Union 501, Int'l Assn. of Bridge, 1959 (Box 438, Folder 4)
  (Atlantic Wire & Iron Works) Boston, MA
- 1-CC-219; Local 1099, International Longshoremen's Association, Independent & B. A. James F. Walsh & V. P. Daniel J. Donovan, 1959 (Box 438, Folder 5)
  (Furness-Withy Co.) Wilmington & E. Boston, MA
- 1-CC-227; United Slate, Tar & Composition Roofers, Damp & Waterproof Workers Association, Local 105 & Sam Klein, 1959 (Box 438, Folder 6)
  (J. B. Lowell, Inc.) Worcester, MA
- 1-CC-228; Local 719 of International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, & Business Agent, John Ahern, 1959 (Box 438, Folder 7)
  (Blanchard Stebbins, Inc.) Manchester, NH
- 1-CC-229; Local Union 40 of Sheet Metal Workers International Assoc. & Henry Silverman, Bus. Rep., 1959 (Box 438, Folder 8)
  (Anemostat Corporation of America) Hartford, CT
- 1-CC-230; Int'l Bro. of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen & Helpers of America Local 671 & Raymond Murphy, B. R., 1959 (Box 438, Folder 9)
  (Frank Amodio Moving & Storage Co.) Hartford, CT
- 1-CC-231; Local 82, Teamsters, International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen & Helpers of America, 1959 (Box 438, Folder 10)
  (Custom Cut Corporation) Boston, MA
- 1-CC-232; Local 677, International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen & Helpers of America, 1959 (Box 438, Folder 11)
  (The Sigliano Lumber Company, Inc.) Waterbury, CT
- 1-CC-234; Larry Salvucchi & International Brotherhood of Operating Engineers & Local 4, 1959 (Box 438, Folder 12)
  (Ivan M. Hanscom) Bangor, ME
- 1-CC-235; Int'l Bro. of Teamsters, Local 671 & Raymond Murphy, Bus. Rep., 1959 (Box 438, Folder 13)
  (Frank Amodio Moving & Storage Co., Inc.) Hartford, CT
- 1-CC-237; Local 559, Teamsters et al., 1959 (Box 438, Folder 14)
  (Hartford Gen. Tire, A Sub. Of General Tire & Rubber Company of Akron, OH) Hartford, CT
- 1-CC-238; Local 57, International Union of Operating Engineers & Business Agent Malone, 1959 (Box 438, Folder 15)
  (J. L. Marshall & Sons, Inc.) Providence, RI
- 1-CC-335; Local 1333, International Brotherhood of Painters, Decorators & Paperhangers of America & Bus. Agt. Carmino "Tom" Raspallo, 1963 (Box 439, Folder 1)
  (Pittsburgh Plate Glass Company)
- 1-CC-338; Pipefitters of Boston Local 537, UA, 1963 (Box 439, Folder 2)
  (N. D. C. Construction Co. Inc.) Boston, MA
- 1-CC-340; Local 800 of International Longshoremen's Association, Thomas McNiff, Business Agent, 1963 (Box 439, Folder 3)
  (Wiggin Terminals, Inc.) South Boston, MA
- 1-CC-341; Framingham-Newton Building & Construction Trades Council, Local 609 Construction & General Laborers Union, 1963 (Box 439, Folder 4)
  (Midas Development Corp.) Dedham, MA
- 1-CC-342; Local 709, ILA & Daniel Doherty, B. A. & International Longshoremen's Assoc., 1963 (Box 439, Folder 5)
  (Wiggin Terminals, Inc.) Cambridge & Revere, MA
- 1-CC-343; Local 98, International Union of Operating Engineers, 1963 (Box 439, Folder 6)
  (New England Survey Service, Inc.) Springfield, MA
- 1-CC-344; Plumbers & Fitters Union Local 626 a/w United Association of Journeymen & Apprentices of Plumbing & Pipe Fitting Ind. Of US & Canada, 1962 (Box 439, Folder 7)
  (Poorvu Construction Co., Inc.)
- 1-CC-345; Local 800, ILA & Thomas McNiff B.A., Int'l Longshoremen's Assn. John F. Moran, V.P., Local 799 ILA & Agt. Daniel Doherty & Local 805 ILA & David B. Flynn B.A., 1963 (Box 439, Folder 8)
  (Terminal Operators Inc.) Boston, Revere, Winthrop & Cambridge., MA
- 1-CC-346; Building & Construction Trades Council of Metropolitan Dist., International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen & Helpers, Bldg. & Excavators Local 379, 1963 (Box 439, Folder 9)
  (County Seat Caf, Inc.) Boston, MA
- 1-CC-347; International Hod Carriers, Bldg. & Common Laborers Un. Local 223 & 379, International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen & Helpers of Am., 1963 (Box 439, Folder 10)
  (89 State Street, Inc.) Boston, MA
- 1-CC-348; Hartford Building & Construction Trades Council of Hartford & Vicinity, 1963 (Box 439, Folder 11)
  (Plaza Incorporated) Hartford, CT
- 1-CC-349; Plumbers & Fitters Union Local 537 a/w United Association of Plumbing & Pipefitting Industry of US & Canada, 1963 (Box 439, Folder 12)
  (Kirkland Construction Co., Inc.) Boston, MA
- 1-CC-350; Local 4, Hoisting & Portable Engineers, Int'l Union of Operating Engineers, 1963 (Box 439, Folder 13)
  (Jefferson Construction Company) Boston, MA
- 1-CC-351; Building & Construction Trades Council of Metropolitan District, 1963 (Box 439, Folder 14)
- 1-CC-352; Building Service Employees Int'l Union Local 516 & Frank Ryan, 1963 (Box 439, Folder 15)
  (The William J. Burns Int'l Detective Agency, Inc.) Boston, MA
- 1-CC-353; Local 90, International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers & Bernard Gilbride, Agent Local 90, 1963 (Box 439, Folder 16)
  (Richard W. Kilpatrick, Inc.) New Haven, CT
- 1-CC-354; Brewery Workers Union 8 of International Union of United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, Soft Drink & Distillery Workers of America, 1963 (Box 439, Folder 17)
  (Burlington Handling, Inc., Bert P. Williams, Inc.) Roxbury, MA
- 1-CC-355; Glaziers Local 1044 a/w Brotherhood of Painters, Decorators & Paperhangers of America, 1963 (Box 439, Folder 18)
  (Blanchard Stebbins, Inc.) Boston, MA
- 1-CC-356; International Ladies' Garment Workers, 1963 (Box 439, Folder 19)
  (F. R. Knitting Mills, Inc.) Fall River, MA
- 1-CC-357; Local 7, International Association of Bridge et al., 1963 (Box 439, Folder 20)
  (Perini Corporation) Boston, MA
- 1-CC-358; Local 7, International Assoc. of Bridge, Structural & Ornam. Ironworkers, 1963 (Box 440, Folder 1)
  (Bowman Steel Corp.) Reading, MA
- 1-CC-361; Seafood Worker's Union, Local 2 Series 1572 a/w International Longshoremen's Association, 1963 (Box 440, Folder 2)
  (Fulham Brothers, Inc.) Boston, MA
- 1-CC-362; Local 4, Hoisting & Portable Engineers, International Union of Operating Engineers, 1963 (Box 440, Folder 3)
  (Consolidated Constructors, Inc.) Boston, MA
- 1-CC-363; Int'l Assoc. of Bridge, Structural & Ornamental Iron Workers, Local 474, 1963 (Box 440, Folder 4)
  (Structural Concrete Corporation) Manchester, NH
- 1-CC-365; Hoisting & Portable Engineers, Loc. 4 et al., 1963 (Box 440, Folder 5)
  (Hugh Nawn, Inc.) Boston, MA
- 1-CC-366; Local 15, Bricklayers, Masons & Plasterers International Union, 1963 (Box 440, Folder 6)
  (Martin W. Manzelli Corp.) Waltham, MA
- 1-CC-367; Bricklayers Local Union 51 & William McKeown, Business Agent, 1963 (Box 440, Folder 7)
  (Flatley Construction Corporation) Framingham, MA
- 1-CC-369; United Slate, Tile & Composition Roofers, Damp & Waterproof Workers Association, Local Union 33 & Agent John J. Daley, 1963 (Box 440, Folder 8)
  (Patrick Ross d/b/a Patrick Ross Co.) Cambridge, MA
- 1-CC-371; Bricklayers, Local 52 & Bus. Agent Carmine D'Olimpio, 1963 (Box 440, Folder 9)
  (John F. Kelley) Quincy, MA
- 1-CC-372; International Union of Elevator Constructors, 1963 (Box 440, Folder 10)
- 1-CC-373; Bricklayers Local Union 3, 1963 (Box 440, Folder 11)
  (Colony Construction Co., Inc.) Peabody, MA
- 1-CC-374; United Slate & Composition Roofers, Damp & Waterproof Workers Association, Local Un. 33 & Agt. John J. Daley, 1963 (Box 440, Folder 12)
  (Patrick Ross d/b/a Patrick Ross Co.) Boston, MA
- 1-CC-375; United Brotherhood of Carpenters & Joiners of America, Local 33, 1963 (Box 440, Folder 13)
  (Stanley J. Glod, Inc.) Boston, MA
- 1-CC-376; Int'l Union of Operating Engineers Local 4 & Bus. Agent Carl Bucci, 1963 (Box 440, Folder 14)
  (Gil Bern Construction Corp.) Boston, MA
- 1-CC-377; Teamsters Local 443 a/w International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen & Helpers of America, Ind., 1963 (Box 440, Folder 15)
  (Glendale Steel Corporation of New England) New Haven, CT
- 1-CC-378; Local 385, Amalgamated Meat Cutters & Butcher Workmen of America, 1963 (Box 440, Folder 16)
  (Hillcrest Poultry Industries, Inc.) Auburn, ME
- 1-CC-379; United Steelworkers of America & Agents Sidney Larsen & Herbert Gurney, 1963 (Box 440, Folder 17)
  (Independent Nail Corporation) Providence, RI
- 1-CC-382; Local 175, Bldg. & Construction Laborers & Bus. Rep. John A. Fusco, 1963 (Box 440, Folder 18)
  (Clemens Construction Company, Inc.) Lawrence, MA
- 1-CC-383; Bldg. & Construction Trades Council of Metropolitan District & Agt. John E. Deadey, 1963 (Box 440, Folder 19)
  (Coleman Bros. Corp.) Boston, MA